Class of 1942 Records, 1938-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Class of 1942 Records
1938-[ongoing]
Smith College. Class of 1942.
RG 80 UUID:4e121a60-b2a2-47da-8bb5-34cafdebccfb
13 boxes, 1 microfilm reel (7.3 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1942.
Historical Note
The Class of 1942 was the sixty-fourth graduating class of Smith College.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Class of 1942 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1942, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, questionnaires, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Researchers must sign an access form to use the microfilm for the Class of 1942's 15th [1957] reunion questionnaires.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives. Researchers must sign an access form to use the microfilm for the Class of 1942's 15th [1957] reunion questionnaires.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1942 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Commencement 1942 (Box 2130, Folder 1)
- Commencement Music 1942 (Box 2130, Folder 2)
- Commencement Photographs 1942 (Box 2130, Folder 3)
- Commencement Speaker 1942 (Box 2130, Folder 4)
- Freshman Handbook 1938-1939 (Box 2130, Folder 5)
- Groups 1938-1942 (Box 2130, Folder 6)
- Hoop Rolling 1942 (Box 2130, Folder 7)
- Ivy Day-Photographs 1942 (Box 2130, Folder 8)
- Junior Prom 1941 (Box 2130, Folder 9)
- Junior Ushers 1941 (Box 2130, Folder 10)
- Class Letters 1943-2002 (Box 2130, Folder 11)
- Class Officers 1938-1942 (Box 2130, Folder 12)
- Reunions 1947 (Box 2130, Folder 13)
- Reunions 1952 (Box 2130, Folder 14)
- Reunions 1957 (Box 2130, Folder 15)
- 15th reunion questionnaires [microfilm] 1957 (Box 2130, Folder microfilm)
  Researchers must sign an access form to use the microfilm for the Class of 1942's 15th [1957] reunion questionnaires.
- Reunions 1962 (Box 2130, Folder 16)
- Reunions 1967 (Box 2130, Folder 17)
- Reunions 1972 (Box 2130, Folder 18)
- Reunions 1977-1982 (Box 2130, Folder 19)
- Reunions 1980 (Box 2130, Folder 20)
- Reunions 1987 (Box 2130, Folder 21)
- Reunions 1992 (Box 2130, Folder 22)
- Reunions 1997 (Box 2130, Folder 23)
- Sophomore Carnival 1940 (Box 2131, Folder 1)
- Sophomore Push Committee 1940 (Box 2131, Folder 2)
- Reunion Questionnaire 1992 (Box 2132, Folder 1)
- Reunion Questionnaire: A-D 1992 (Box 2132, Folder 2)
- Reunion Questionnaire: E-H 1992 (Box 2132, Folder 3)
- Reunion Questionnaire: I-L 1992 (Box 2132, Folder 4)
- Reunion Questionnaire: M-P 1992 (Box 2132, Folder 5)
- Reunion Questionnaire: Q-T 1992 (Box 2132, Folder 6)
- Reunion Questionnaire: U-Z 1992 (Box 2132, Folder 7)
- Reunion Questionnaire: Anonymous 1992 (Box 2132, Folder 8)
- Reunion Questionnaire: Anonymous 1992 (Box 2132, Folder 9)
- Reunion Questionnaire: Anonymous 1992 (Box 2132, Folder 10)
- Reunion Questionnaire: Anonymous 1992 (Box 2132, Folder 11)
- Reunion Questionnaire: Anonymous 1992 (Box 2132, Folder 12)
- Reunion Questionnaire: Anonymous 1992 (Box 2132, Folder 13)
- Reunion Questionnaire: Anonymous 1992 (Box 2132, Folder 14)